📋 Privacy Policy
=================

##### Updated on 15/06/2022

Scope of The Agreement
----------------------

Thanks for using UpBox.me! Here we describe how we collect, use, and handle your personal data when you use our websites, software, and services (“Services”).

What & Why
----------

We collect and use the following information to provide, improve, protect, and promote our Services.

_Account information._ We collect, and associate with your account, the information you provide to us when you do things such as sign up for your account, upgrade to a paid plan, and set up two-factor authentication (like your name, email address, phone number, payment info, and physical address).

_Your Stuff._ Our Services are designed as a simple and personalized way for you to store your files, documents, photos, comments, messages, and so on (“Your Stuff”), collaborate with others, and work across multiple devices and services. To make that possible, we store, process, and transmit Your Stuff as well as information related to it. This related information includes your profile information that makes it easier to collaborate and share Your Stuff with others, as well as things like the size of the file, the time it was uploaded, collaborators, and usage activity.

_Usage information._ We collect information related to how you use the Services, including actions you take in your account (like sharing, editing, viewing, creating and moving files or folders). We use this information to provide, improve, and promote our Services, and protect UpBox.me users. Please refer to our FAQ for more information about how we use this usage information.

_Device information._ We also collect information from and about the devices you use to access the Services. This includes things like IP addresses, the type of browser and device you use, the web page you visited before coming to our sites, and identifiers associated with your devices. Your devices (depending on their settings) may also transmit location information to the Services. For example, we use device information to detect abuse and identify and troubleshoot bugs.

_Cookies and other technologies._ We use technologies like cookies and pixel tags to provide, improve, protect, and promote our Services. For example, cookies help us with things like remembering your username for your next visit, understanding how you are interacting with our Services, and improving them based on that information. You can set your browser to not accept cookies, but this may limit your ability to use the Services. We may also use third-party service providers that set cookies and similar technologies to promote UpBox.me services.

_Marketing._ We give users the option to use some of our Services free of charge. These free Services are made possible by the fact that some users upgrade to one of our paid Services. If you register for our Services, we will, from time to time, send you information about upgrades when permissible. Users who receive these marketing materials can opt out at any time. If you don’t want to receive a particular type of marketing material from us, click the ‘unsubscribe’ link in the corresponding emails, or update your preferences in the Notifications section of your personal account.

We sometimes contact people who don’t have a UpBox.me account. For recipients in the EU, we or a third party will obtain consent before reaching out. If you receive an email and no longer wish to be contacted by UpBox.me, you can unsubscribe and remove yourself from our contact list via the message itself.

Bases for processing your data. We collect and use the personal data described above in order to provide you with the Services in a reliable and secure manner. We also collect and use personal data for our legitimate business needs. To the extent we process your personal data for other purposes, we ask for your consent in advance or require that our partners obtain such consent.

With Whom
---------

We may share information as discussed below, but we won’t sell it to advertisers or other third parties.

Others working for and with UpBox.me. UpBox.me uses certain trusted third parties (for example, providers of customer support and IT services) for the business purposes of helping us provide, improve, protect, and promote our Services. These third parties will access your information to perform tasks on our behalf, and we’ll remain responsible for their handling of your information per our instructions. For a list of trusted third parties that we use to process your personal data and more details on the categories of personal information that we’ve disclosed, please see our FAQ.

Other users. Our Services are designed to help you collaborate with others. If you register your UpBox.me account with an email address on a domain owned by your employer or organization, join a UpBox.me Business Team, or collaborate with other UpBox.me users, we may suggest you or your team as a potential collaborator to other users or teams. For example, if you interact with a person at a company, and that person frequently works with one of their coworkers, we may suggest you as a potential collaborator for that coworker. Collaborators and potential collaborators may see some of your basic information, like your name, UpBox.me Business Team name, profile picture, device, email address, and usage information. This helps you sync up with teams you can join and helps other users share files and folders with you.

Certain features let you make additional information available to others.

Law & Order and the Public Interest. We may disclose your information to third parties if we determine that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (a) comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or appropriate government request; (b) protect any person from death or serious bodily injury; (c) prevent fraud or abuse of UpBox.me or our users; (d) protect UpBox.me’s rights, property, safety, or interest; or (e) perform a task carried out in the public interest.

Stewardship of your data is critical to us and a responsibility that we embrace. We believe that your data should receive the same legal protections regardless of whether it’s stored on our Services or on your home computer’s hard drive. We’ll abide by the following Government Request Principles when receiving, scrutinizing, and responding to government requests (including national security requests) for your data:

Be transparent Fight blanket requests Protect all users, and Provide trusted services. We publish a Transparency Report as part of our commitment to informing you about when and how governments ask us for information. This report details the types and numbers of requests we receive from law enforcement. We encourage you to review our Government Request Principles and Transparency Report for more detailed information on our approach and response to government requests.

How
---

Security. We have a team dedicated to keeping your information secure and testing for vulnerabilities. We continue to work on features to keep your information safe in addition to things like two-factor authentication, encryption of files at rest, and alerts when new devices and apps are linked to your account. We deploy automated technologies to detect abusive behavior and content that may harm our Services, you, or other users.

User Controls. You can access, amend, download, and delete your personal information by logging into your UpBox.me account and going to your account settings page. Learn more here about managing your account information generally, or click here to learn how to change your profile information.

Retention. When you sign up for an account with us, we’ll retain information you store on our Services for as long as your account exists or as long as we need it to provide you the Services. If you delete your account, we’ll initiate deletion of this information after 30 days. Learn more here. But please note: (1) there might be some latency in deleting this information from our servers and back-up storage; and (2) we may retain this information if necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, or enforce our agreements.

Where
-----

Around the world. To provide you with the Services, we may store, process, and transmit data in the United States and locations around the world—including those outside your country. Data may also be stored locally on the devices you use to access the Services.

Data Transfers. When transferring data from the European Union, the European Economic Area, the United Kingdom, and Switzerland, UpBox.me relies upon a variety of legal mechanisms, such as contracts with our customers and affiliates, [Standard Contractual Clauses](https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/international-dimension-data-protection/standard-contractual-clauses-scc_en), and the European Commission's [adequacy decisions](https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/international-dimension-data-protection/adequacy-decisions_en) about certain countries, as applicable.

EU-U.S. Privacy Shield and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield. UpBox.me complies with the EU-U.S. and Swiss–U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data transferred from the European Union, the European Economic Area, the United Kingdom, and Switzerland to the United States, although UpBox.me does not rely on the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield or Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks as a legal basis for transfers of personal data. UpBox.me has certified to the Department of Commerce that it, and its subsidiary JN Projects Inc. d/b/a HelloSign, adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles with respect to such data. You can also learn more about Privacy Shield at https://www.privacyshield.gov.

UpBox.me is subject to oversight by the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. JAMS is the US-based independent organization responsible for reviewing and resolving complaints about our Privacy Shield compliance—free of charge to you. We ask that you first submit any such complaints directly to us via [\[email protected\]](https://upbox.me/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). If you aren’t satisfied with our response, please contact JAMS at https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield. In the event your concern still isn’t addressed by JAMS, you may be entitled to a binding arbitration under Privacy Shield and its principles.

Your Control and Access of Your Data
------------------------------------

You have control over your personal data and how it’s collected, used, and shared. For example, you can:

Delete Your Stuff in your UpBox.me account. Change or correct personal data. You can manage your account and the content contained in it, as well as edit some of your personal data, through your account settings page. Access and take your data elsewhere. You can access your personal data from your UpBox.me account and you can download a copy of Your Stuff in a machine readable format as outlined here. You can also ask us for a copy of personal data you provided to us or that we’ve collected, the business or commercial purpose for collecting it, the types of sources we got it from, and types of third parties we’ve shared it with. Object to the processing of your personal data. Depending on the processing activity, you can request that we stop or limit processing of your personal data. If you would like to submit a data access request or object to the processing of your personal data, please email us at [\[email protected\]](https://upbox.me/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). To request that your personal data be deleted, please fill out this form. For more information on how to control and access your personal data, please see our FAQ.

UpBox.me as controller or processor. If you reside in North America (the United States, Canada, and Mexico), UpBox.me, Inc. acts as your service provider. For all other users, UpBox.me International Unlimited Company acts as a controller of your personal data. If you are a UpBox.me Business or Education customer outside of North America, UpBox.me acts as a processor of your data.

Jurisdiction
------------

UpBox.me is the product of the company "Axel Hardy" which is registered in France with registration number 79233972300035.

* Legal address: Route de la magne, 74410 Saint Jorioz, FRANCE
* Contact e-mail: [\[email protected\]](https://upbox.me/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

The governing law is the legislation of France.

Changes
-------

UpBox.me owns the right to change and update this document occasionally, and review it at least once per year. If you continue using The App, then you also agree to comply with all the further versions of this document.

© Copyright 2024 UpBox.me  
[Terms of Use](https://upbox.me/terms) - [Privacy Policy](https://upbox.me/privacy)
